MY BELOVED DEMON
NOTICE OF SALVATION FOR…
HELP, SOS!
SOS IZ:
334 PANPO-TON, SOCHO-KU, SEOUL
The subscriber you are calling
does not answer.
Not ready yet?
TEMPORARILY NOT WORKING
I have to get up immediately.
STAIRCASE: BLACK PASS
No…
No!
To To Hee, please…
No, please!
Please stop!
No!
Please!
Jung Ku Won.
To To Hee.
To To Hee
is everything ok
Everything is fine.
Everything is over.
EPISODE 6
WHEEL OF FORTUNE
Thank you
Are you sure you don't want to go to the doctor?
There is no one here.
But the electronic lock is broken.
He enjoyed it.
He seemed to be enjoying himself
from my horror.
As if he came to see me die.
And…
that song
Killing me wasn't his only goal.
He was going to catch the prey,
which I have already missed many times.
He must have been delighted.
You seem to have a good understanding of
as killers think.
I understand how predators think.
My phone
Here he is.
He was on the floor.
It's not him.
This is another person.
- What?
- He does not look like
who tried to kill you before.
Then maybe more than one person…
Hold on.
Are those scratches on his neck?
The driver also had them.
is it possible
that he changes his face?
That's why I couldn't find him.
I didn't see his real face.
That is, how does he change his face?
Some kind of disguise?
Mr. Chong
You two are hiding something from me.
How did you save To Hee?
She was hanging on the railing,
so how did you two end up on the stairs…
If you are so interested,
ask her yourself.
I'm asking you because she doesn't say.
Then I'm sure she is
has reasons for that.
To Hee has been lonely since childhood,
therefore it is independent
and does not share problems.
That's why she doesn't tell me.
But I have to know what exactly she is going through.
And what gives you this right?
I am the only one on her side.
What do you mean by
are you on her side?
It hurts me when she hurts
i am happy when she is happy.
I don't know where I end up
and it begins.
That's what I mean.
so tell me
what she is hiding from me now.
Don't worry.
You are not the only one on her side.
is everything ok
what are you doing here
Still
I took death so lightly.
Not because I'm brave
and because I didn't understand
like this: actually die.
The feeling that the world
which you believed in, disappears...
and you remain completely alone.
He always…
was waiting nearby to kill me.
The security guard, with whom I greeted in the morning,
the employee I spoke with yesterday…
He could have been anyone.
tomorrow
he will wait again with a new face.
Don't drive anymore
this dangerous battle alone.
To Hee
Let's get married.
You don't have to be alone.
How about…
marry me instead?
"MIRE NUTRITION"
Don't drive anymore
this dangerous battle alone.
Let's get married.
How about…
marry me instead?
I need time to think.
DESIGN SAMPLES
Undoubtedly, life is a series of choices.
Let's decide based on feedback
in the country and abroad.
Yes, ma'am.
She thinks about me
compared to some person?
YOUNG LEADER CHOO SOK HOON,
GENERAL DIRECTOR OF "MIRE INVESTMENTS"
What?
Let's meet. Look around.
What kind of meeting is this?
Are we spies?
Who knows what that robot secretary is
will he do to me if he sees?
My neck still hurts from her blow.
You are exaggerating too much.
Yes, yes!
A lunch that Pok Kyo prepared with love.
You can cry emotionally.
Ka Yeon sent you?
- No.
- Then why are you here?
You flew out during rehearsal
and didn't come back all night, so Star Chin...
No, I was madly worried.
You are a spy.
Devil.
Why did you fly out like that in the first place?
It's like a fire has been lit under you.
To To Hee this time
could really die.
But thanks to this we learned
that the attacker hides his face.
Then I studied To To Hee.
But that's not news to anyone, is it?
"Mire's heiress was refused
at the speed of light."
Such a killer headline.
That's not the point.
It was I who confessed this time.
I confessed to her.
- Is it clear?
- What?
Did you confess to her?
Why would you do that after
how did you deny her with the speed of light?
It seems that this is no longer news to anyone.
You said marriage to a man is madness.
So why?
What suddenly made you change your mind?
Just…
It would be indecent all the time
hold a married woman by the wrist.
Such morality from a demon?
Why not?
Let's find out everything.
That is, you will
a married demon?
What is it?
When Star Chin finds out
hell will break out.
I gasped for breath in vain.
So it doesn't bother you?
If you marry Mrs. To,
you will break many hearts.
Let's see.
Social life…
It doesn't matter now.
And love life is important.
Given recent events,
maybe I'll be pampered.
"Hermit"?
This is wrong.
Probably, she chose the card too carelessly.
I will try again.
Just not again!
Is "The Hermit" so bad?
Of course.
It means antiquity,
who has not met for a long time.
It could be worse
after all, I am against the devilish Mrs. To...
Come to my office.
It was necessary to think about social life.
Ms. Choi, good luck in the room of truth.
Sometimes she is out of this world.
I heard a rumor.
Madam, this is a false rumor.
I can criticize to the face
but never behind.
I heard
you are excellent at tarot cards.
I'm sorry…
Give?
This one?
No.
And?
You don't have to be so careful.
Don't be fooled.
"Wheel of Fortune"?
This map
usually means reunion.
Give more details.
Although our fate may repeat itself
by the will and command of heaven,
the direction in which it moves
depends on the will and mind of a person.
This is what it means.
What does this Roman numeral mean?
This is the tenth card.
The number ten means completeness,
symbolizing at the same time the end
and a new beginning.
"The end and a new beginning"?
So delicious?
I have to eat well
to survive when hell breaks loose.
The person who cooked it
great cook.
Pok Kyo, you are officially ready to get married.
I say this not only because
that i made it
but the meat is perfectly cooked
between medium and rare.
Greetings Seok Hoon.
What is it?
Why flowers?
Here.
I wondered what you would think
the bouquet is too banal.
But I'm so embarrassed
which turned out to be completely devoid of flowers.
Everything happened too fast.
Would you like something to drink?
Yes. That is, no.
I've already had a drink.
how is your hand
Everything is fine.
What a relief.
This is funny.
Why are we so embarrassed?
why are you laughing
What is so funny here?
Director Jon, are you jealous?
Jealous?
I have never understood why people are jealous.
And then he realized
that no longer understands itself.
Here is Ms. Sin.
Hey, it's mine.
i still remember
what a rebel you were
when we first met as teenagers.
Just to think that you have revealed yourself to me.
You've come a long way, Seok Hoon.
I was in high school though.
You were still in junior high school, Toto.
Just to think that you will get married.
Unbelievable.
I know
It's hard for me to believe.
I will get married.
Regarding my marriage proposal.
It wasn't just a whim.
When I only heard
that you were on a blind date
my heart dropped.
And I was so jealous
when you confessed to Mr. Chong.
Then I realized
how i feel about you now
not the same as before.
I came here not to pressure you
but it seems he did.
Simply
it surprised me.
I always considered you family.
Now let's become a real family.
If you need marriage,
let's become a family first.
And then let's not hurry
and we'll figure it all out.
I can wait.
The satisfaction…
Exactly what is needed.
Looks like you're getting used to office life.
Why do people drink this junk?
Listen, I have a question.
What does it mean when a person
save someone as an emergency contact?
This means…
that a person trusts another more,
than everyone else.
"100 TIPS FOR FIRST LOVE"
- Really?
- Yes.
More than everyone else?
Hold on.
And Choo Seong-hoon?
This is bad.
give me this
Page 125.
So you came to me, not To To Hee?
This is an equal business relationship.
You are so informal
contact the employer.
Our relationship was personal,
before becoming professional.
You refused her.
Why are you bowing to her now?
I don't like marriage, not To To Hee.
Don't play with her emotions.
You know better than anyone,
in which she is now in despair.
unfortunately
I'm not kidding either.
Mr. Chon, Mrs. To leaves.
Please excuse me. Work.
remember your place
you are a guard, don't cross the line.
There are no boundaries that I cannot cross.
Can I ask you something?
Why did you save me and Choo Seok Hoon
like emergency contacts?
you are my keeper
and Seok Hoon is like family to me.
What about you?
Why did you confess to me?
You turned me down before
with the speed of light.
Why is everyone asking the same thing?
Just like that.
Noh Sook Min, head of Mire Group
will make a speech
at the laying of the first stone.
CEREMONY OF LAYING THE FIRST STONE
2ND MIRE GROUP FACTORY IN CHONAN - 2023
I am thrilled to finally be standing here.
Ambitions of "Mire Group"
regarding the second factory in Chonan
immeasurable
This factory will ensure safe supply
high-quality packaging materials...
What is she doing here?
My dear.
We will continue to prepare "Mire Group"...
Why so surprised?
You never come to events like that.
You consider them superficial.
Sometimes superficial actions
can do a lot.
...sincerely thank everyone,
who supported us along the way,
including Mayor Ahn Chin Suk
and MP Song U Chan.
Thank you.
The presenter made a mistake.
you are not the head
and acting chairman.
We should not advertise
what a precarious position we are in, huh?
So it wasn't a mistake.
I'm getting married tomorrow.
Let's move on to the main event
today's ceremony,
symbolic laying of the stone.
I didn't have time
prepare wedding invitations.
But you understand, right?
After all, we are family.
You are so clumsy.
My health is above all else
even in important moments of life.
Can't miss the daily rituals, right?
I hope I won't get distracted later
and I will not cry.
I can, right?
Please find out
support in the comments.
Like, comment, subscribe
and press the bell.
UKPD
Yes?
It doesn't sound right.
That's what YouTubers say now.
UKPD!
Great, ma'am.
The first part of the ceremony is composed
from the procession, bows,
vows, exchange of wedding rings,
marriage announcement
festive songs and speeches,
completion of the service and photo session.
The second part is composed
from the entrance of the couple, cutting the cake,
champagne rain, welcoming guests...
Let everything be simple.
I just wanted to live up to expectations
head of Chu.
Then please simplify a little.
I will let you know.
It will be such a hit.
Exclusive report about the wedding!
"To To Hee Drink" is already in the results
search for your wedding request!
That's great.
Allow me to share a message,
to support
and you didn't get upset or cry.
- Are you afraid?
- Thank you, madam.
Mrs. To!
You have never been so beautiful.
I'm serious, Ms. To!
What do you say, Ms. Chu?
Are you satisfied now?
Did you want it?
What about the dress?
Couldn't you have chosen a more elegant one?
I know it's an arranged marriage
but how could you allow
secretary to choose a dress?
After all, it's your wedding.
It should reflect your taste.
It is your taste that distinguishes you.
You will always make me angry.
If you continue like this,
stay alone
Who would say
You are the loneliest in the family.
Can't say anything good?
After all, this is my wedding.
Here's something I learned from plants.
When two mutants breed,
then the offspring are not mutants.
Isn't that incredible?
An amazing mystery of nature.
Such a combination is also desirable in marriage.
You two are a good example.
Because you two are the most incredible mutants.
You should sign us.
I excluded you because you would bore everyone.
Devil's gallows.
You can't be so cruel to a dead person.
How is it there?
How are you?
Do you even know where I am?
Let's see.
They say the rich can't
get to heaven
so you are not there.
You can't even be in hell
because you are a better person than you pretend to be.
Where did you go then, Ms. Chu?
Leaving me alone here.
I'm in your memories.
Where else should I be?
Are you ready, ladies?
Wish me luck with the riddle.
You did it.
you are here I didn't expect you to come.
As I said, we are family.
You look great in the dress.
Mom would be so happy
see you today
It's a shame she can't be here.
Congratulations. Sincerely.
Thank you. Sincerely.
Sit there.
See how she triumphs.
When will you release the story?
Today is a happy day.
Let him enjoy.
Time to congratulate the star of the day.
- Where is my place?
- Here is the bride.
Please, all sincerely congratulate the bride.
Why did you confess to me?
Just like that.
I don't want you to die.
I'm taking you now
my dearest and most beautiful bride,
To To Hee, for a wife.
I take you now, my dearest
and the most handsome groom,
Jung Ku Won, for her husband.
I will be there in happiness and in trouble
and I will always put you first.
I will take
I will respect and love you as such
what are you
Prenuptial contract?
I made a simple contract.
"Parties A and B will surrender"…
"Parties A and B will surrender
in public as a perfect couple."
"Privately, both parties will respect the boundaries
They will not interfere
into each other's space."
"The parties will make efforts
to cooperate for their purpose."
"The contract will be completed...
…when both parties
will achieve their goal."
SIDE A: TO TO HI
SIDE B: JEONG KOO WON
Bride and groom now
will pass through the central passage,
taking the first steps into the world as a couple.
It symbolizes their vow
walk side by side for the rest of our lives...
Stop!
Wait a second. Sorry.
This was not according to the agreement: "the rest of life"?
This is a traditional saying.
Just play along.
No.
As a demon, I take deals very seriously.
The rest of my life is extremely long.
Sorry.
Remove the "rest of life".
Yes, ma'am.
The pair will pass through the central aisle.
It doesn't matter at all.
Congratulations to the bride and groom!
Please support me in welcoming them.
He's too handsome to be a bodyguard.
You are ugly!
Ms. Choi, you can
really applaud?
I was hoping for another pair.
Which one?
Me and Mr. Chong.
Why are you so happy, Su An?
The higher you fly, the harder you fall.
What is it?
Nothing.
Turn to each other
and show love!
Make more effort, can you?
Is that enough?
This is too much. Go easy.
How picky.
Director Chong is really the best.
You seem to be implying
that Ms. To is no better.
I didn't imply that
but I will not correct you.
Here you go.
And more.
kiss!
It's personal.
I heard you married him
for the sake of inheritance.
A kiss is not a problem.
Is it really necessary?
"Parties A and B will surrender
in public as a perfect couple."
ok
here's to you
Time for one photo at a time.
Let's start with the groom.
Sok Hune.
Looks like I wasn't good enough.
Not at all.
You are just perfect.
for me
you will always be family
which I can rely on.
I'm always on your side, To Hee.
Thank you.
Although Mr. Jeong is equally rude to everyone,
he's good to you, right?
It is difficult to describe it
as good or bad.
Is that what you like, Ms. Xin?
Let's go home, dear.
"Beloved"?
Is "sweet" better?
See you soon.
Oh, don't look at a married woman
with such crazy emotions.
Eyes everywhere!
When will it be my turn?
YOUNG PEOPLE
THE BIRTH OF THE CINDERELLA MAN…
EXCLUSIVE REPORT
Has she found out yet?
I thought she would
too preoccupied with rehearsal.
Ms. Chin, please open the door.
- And has she been like this for a long time?
- Well...
Star Chin, I was going to tell you
- before the press conference itself.
- Shut up.
I am more angry with you than with him.
Their marriage
just a peaceful way to preserve his powers.
What is peaceful in marriage?
This is the apogee of cruelty.
You'll be back, right?
I trust you, Star Chin!
She is a professional
so will definitely be back.
Your fingerprint is registered.
What if the lock breaks again?
This one is almost impossible to crack.
come in
So this is where To To Hee lives.
Let me explain something.
I had to move here
because an intruder can break in...
Careful, To To Hee!
Has the villain already broken in?
What was he looking for to make such a mess?
I was recently
preoccupied with preparations for the wedding.
Just sit anywhere.
So no one broke in here?
Do not exaggerate.
Cute and homely, don't you think?
Give me a wristband.
This is what "at home" looks like.
Finally neat enough
to call home.
Can you cook like that?
I want homemade food.
forget it
I am your husband, not a slave.
Do just one more favor.
I threw away my favorite blouse by mistake.
How could this happen?
TRASHBIN FOR CLOTHES
Not this one.
Here she is.
What? She is spoiled.
No.
- Clean up before entering.
- What do I have...
That blouse seems familiar.
Hurry up!
It will wake me up.
"SUNVOL FOUNDATION"
"SUNVOL FOUNDATION" IN THE OLD NEWSPAPER
"HYUNGMYON DAILY"
JUNE 7, 1977 COMPLETED
CONSTRUCTION OF "SUNVOL THEATER"
Hello, this is Choo Seok Hoon from Mire Investments.
I would like to receive articles
about "Sunvol Foundation".
I am considering an investment opportunity.
You save in the archives
copies of very old issues?
JUNE 7, 1977
Grandma? But she died.
Now everything belongs to my dad,
and will soon become mine.
Nice tattoo.
It suits you.
But To Kyone.
is that you
did you wash
Yes, as you can see.
And you?
I washed
I have never seen you dressed like this.
Each other
Ah, then...
are you going to sleep already?
And what else to do here?
It's time for you to go to bed.
It's already late.
I know
I'm so tired.
What does it mean: "And what else to do here?"
How embarrassing.
good night
To To Hee.
Jung Ku Won.
Young master!
Young Master Yi Sune!
The teacher will come.
You can't go look at the flowers now.
Father will be angry if he finds out...
Everyone will be happy if you keep quiet.
Another dream about those times
when was i human
What's all the fuss so early...
- in the morning?
- Good morning.
No.
what are you doing so early
You are not a fool.
What are you talking about?
Am I too pretty in the morning?
Yes.
No.
You look like you haven't slept
and fought all night.
I haven't slept so well in a long time.
I woke up because I was hungry.
do you want
No, thank you.
A cup of hand-brewed coffee
and I'm fine.
Hand-brewed coffee?
I don't have any. And we don't have time.
How can you not have it?
And why don't we have time? weekend
We have to find the intruder.
I don't want to
The wedding was too troublesome.
I insist on resting now.
But on working days we have a lot of work.
What is his name there?
Choo Seok Hoon or whatever.
He's investigating Mr. Cha, right?
Will investigate faster
a living person, not a dead one.
A living person, who exactly?
we don't even know
what he really looks like.
We will find out who is behind this.
The real attacker,
who is behind what is in the mask.
I have a suspect.
Who?
No Suk Min's son, No To Kyung.
Enough, To Kyoune.
stop it He knocks.
Let go! Ahoy!
I said enough!
Pull him away!
- What's wrong with you?
- Stop it!
Let go immediately.
is everything ok
Open your eyes.
Oh, what the hell?
Time to pretend.
You will not die.
How many more?
I'm going out!
OK. I'm ready
No.
Feeling too famous again?
You have to hide your face
if we want to follow him.
You stand out too much.
You just attract attention.
Oh, why here?
What's up with you now?
So you can kill someone.
Come back when you're ready.
So what if I kill someone?
Come on.
Quick.
If we teleport now,
we will find ourselves in the trunk of his car.
Please keep your distance.
He is very careful.
No, we are just careless.
- And my presence is too noticeable...
- Let's wait a little here.
Where are you?
I quickly go downstairs for an espresso.
don't laugh
- Let's go.
Come on.
Did he park the car and take the subway?
Something is definitely suspicious.
He can't sit still at all, can he?
where is mine
Can they meet at the subway station?
With an attacker in a mask.
"MAGIC LIGHT"
Closed space again?
You're obsessed, right?
hold on
hold for me
I'll have another drink later.
HIDE CAMERA FOR CASH
A hidden camera?
He seems to be extremely cautious.
Haida
What the…
"The parties will make efforts
to cooperate for their goal".
MY BELOVED DEMON
My strength wavered.
The problem is definitely yours.
If someone has a problem,
you have don't blame me
So what kind of marriage is this?
Not that you have a chance,
but you shouldn't get married.
Don't worry!
- Who is this?
- Mr. Who, won't you come back?
Leave it. You kicked me out.
He ran away after one day?
I find you very suspicious, Mr. Chong.
You're not human, are you?
What if Choo Seok Hoon ducks something?
Nothing will prevent the truth from being revealed.
You should always be careful.
Everyone has bad days.
Translation of subtitles: Daria Hochel